[
    {
        "front": "Tabako",
        "back": "Cigarette",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Hoshii",
        "back": "Need, Want  ",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": NaN,
        "back": "<adj.>",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Yōji",
        "back": "Work, appointment",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Suimas",
        "back": "To smoke",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Soshite",
        "back": "And (For sentences)",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Omiyage",
        "back": "Souvenir, Gift",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Nenkan",
        "back": "Period of years",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Senshū",
        "back": "Last week",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Konshū",
        "back": "This week",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Raishū",
        "back": "Next week",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Mata",
        "back": "Again",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Zannen",
        "back": "Unfortunate",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Tokidoki",
        "back": "Sometimes",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Asa",
        "back": "Morning",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Hiru",
        "back": "Noon",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Yoru",
        "back": "Night",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Tanoshii",
        "back": "Enjoyable",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Saikin",
        "back": "Now a days",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Takusan",
        "back": "Too much",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": NaN,
        "back": "<na-adj.>",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Yūgata",
        "back": "Late evening",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Ga / Demo (polite)",
        "back": "But, However",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Hanashimas",
        "back": "To speak",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Kakimas",
        "back": "To write",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Arukimas",
        "back": "To walk",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Imas",
        "back": "To exist (Living things)",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Arimas",
        "back": "To exist (Non-Living things)",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Okimas",
        "back": "To wake up",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Nemas",
        "back": "To sleep",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Hatarakimas",
        "back": "To Work",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Okane",
        "back": "Money",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "~kara / ~node",
        "back": "‘therefore’",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Benri",
        "back": "Convenient\n<na-adj.>",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Shinsetsu",
        "back": "Kind\n<na-adj.>",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Shizuka",
        "back": "Quiet\n<na-adj.>",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Yūmei",
        "back": "Famous\n<na-adj.>",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Kirei",
        "back": "Beautiful\n<na-adj.>",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Yasai",
        "back": "Vegetable",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Tenki",
        "back": "Weather",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Chikatestsu",
        "back": "Subway",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Mō",
        "back": "Already",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Benkyō",
        "back": "Studies",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Kaimas",
        "back": "To buy",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Mekishiko",
        "back": "Mexico",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Toiu",
        "back": "Called as",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Asagohan",
        "back": "Breakfast",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Motteimas",
        "back": "To have",
        "chapter": 7
    },
    {
        "front": "Onegaishimas",
        "back": "to request, to wish, to ask, to beg",
        "chapter": 7
    }
]